#Description

The JWebSwing is a web framework designed for ease of use, and as simplistic as possible in design.
Design your applications the same way you would design a Swing application! Annotate your CSS according to Java Objects, Fields, or even in-line.

Utilizing the best open source available on the web, This framework combines the best components available freely on the web into a single, easy-to-use, and extremely powerful framework which is lightweight, fast, and easily maintainable.

Focusing on a core of JQuery, JQuery UI, JQuery Layout, and Atmosphere Push - You can ensure that your application will run on any browser (Or phone application) with total theming and styling capabilities.

With AJAX at the center, Angular events, directives and modules, events are both server and client capable with ease. 
Utilize adapters and dynamic angular adapters to easily integrate any new features

Plug into any device instantly with cordova and the Dynamic Loader. 

#[JWebSwing Web Site](http://www.armineasy.com) #[JWebSwing API](http://www.armineasy.com/web/javadoc/index.html)

##Categories
Frameworks, Object Oriented, Java, Single-Language,Single-Page, Multi-Page, HTML, CSS, JS, JQuery, JQuery UI, Border Layout, Angular, Bootstrap, JQX, JQXWidgets

##License
* GNU Library or Lesser General Public License version 3.0 (LGPLv3)
* Respective licenses of the frameworks integrated
* JQX Widgets Library Direct Implementation (The commercial license is suitable for commercial websites and projects or a corporate intranet)

##Features

  * Java 8
  * Web Framework
  * Globalization (via Globalize)
  * Complete Server Side Ajax
  * JQuery
  * JQuery.Layouts
  * Bootstrap 4
  * Angular Databinding
  * JQuery UI
  * JQuery Mobile
  * JQuery Themes
  * jqPlot Graphing
  * DataTables
  * C3 Graphing Library
  * NVD3 Graphing Library
  * Many More.....

#Code-Wise
  * Complete Automated Testing and Distribution System [link](http://gedmarc.ddns.net:9080)
  * Quality Gate Controlled Code, Ensuring only the best gets through [link](http://gedmarc.ddns.net:9000)
  
  * HTML/CSS/JS customization according to client browser
  * Atmosphere Server Push
  * Annotated and Programmable CSS Layer
  * Use Swing standards (Adapters, Events, Factories)
  * Lightweight and Compact, Not server intensive, extremely responsive (25 ms)
  * Servlet based (Tested on Servlet 2.0 and 3.0)
  * Garuanteed Layout and interraction regardless of client browser
  * Graphing/B.I. Capabilities
  * Load On Demand Quickly
  * Plug and Play JQuery Component Design